# **SIMONE ANTHONY**

2904 Summit Lake Dr, Stone Mtn, Georgia 30083-6928 ♦ H: (404) 397-9523 ♦ C: 404-397-9523 ♦

Email: simone.anthony1@yahoo.com ♦ LinkedIn: Simone Anthony ♦ Website: <a href="http://www.simoneanthony.com/">http://www.simoneanthony.com/</a>

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

With a strong technical skill-set, attention to detail, and 2+ years of experience, My passion and desire is to work professionally as a Full Stack Web Developer, where I can use my technical knowledge to elevate user experience to the next level. I am passionate about web development and thoroughly enjoy learning about new web technologies. I spend much of my free time studying and expanding my professional knowledge.

#### SKILLS

- Frontend Web Development: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript (ES6), jQuery, Bootstrap, React/Redux.
- Backend Web Development: PHP, C/C++, MySQL/SQL.
- CMS experience: Expression Engine,
   WordPress, Magento 1 and Magento 2.
- Experience with Git, GitHub and Gitlab.
- GreenSock: GSAP Animation and HTML Animated Banners.

- Ability to build HTML emails.
- Experience with Heroku
- API Integration with JavaScript/PHP
- Firm understand of CSS preprocessors (LESS/SASS).
- Knowledge of photo editing software (e.g. Gimp, Photoshop).

WORK HISTORY

#### Front End Developer, 06/2017 to Current

**PureRED** – Stone Mtn, GA

- Developed multiple landing pages using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and iQuery.
- Built HTML emails
- Assisted In building multiple WordPress sites and helped maintain them for multiple clients.
- Assisted in developing and adding to PHP Templates used to minimize development time within the workplace.
- Used Basic SQL and MySQL to Inject data into client Databases
- Introduced to ES6 and React.

## Freelance Web Developer, 01/2016 to 05/2016

## Self Employed – Atlanta, Georgia

- Designed, implemented and monitored web pages and sites for continuous improvement in fast-paced environment.
- Introduced to HTML5, CSS3 JavaScript and jQuery.

EDUCATION —

2019

## **Udemy Certification**

Modern React with Redux [2019 Update]

Issued: Aug 2019

Credential ID: UC-RVNO74AF

Georgia State University - Atlanta, GA

2015-2016; 2019